// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is a correct syntax to output '''Hello World''' in C++?",
    answer: "cout << '''Hello World''';",
    options: [
      "cout << '''Hello World''';",
      "System.out.println('''Hello World''');",
      "Console.WriteLine('''Hello World''');",
      "print ('''Hello World''');"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
    answer: "int x = 5;",
    options: [
      "num x = 5",
      "int x = 5;",
      "x = 5;",
      "double x = 5;"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
    answer: "max(x,y)",
    options: [
      "maxNum(x,y)",
      "max(x,y)",
      "largest(x,y)",
      "maximum(x,y)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "><",
      "==",
      "=",
      "<>"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How do you create a function in C++?",
    answer: "functionName()",
    options: [
      "functionName.",
      "functionName[]",
      "(functionName)",
      "functionName()"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?",
    answer: "MyClass myObj;",
    options: [
      "new myObj = MyClass();",
      "/class myObj = new MyClass();",
      "MyClass myObj;",
      "class MyClass = new myObj();"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How do you start writing an if statement in C++?",
    answer: "if (x > y)",
    options: [
      "if (x > y)",
      "if x > y then:",
      "if x > y:",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
    answer: "return",
    options: [
      "return",
      "get",
      "break",
      "void"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
    answer: "break",
    options: [
      "stop",
      "break",
      "return",
      "exit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How do you create a reference variable of an existing variable?",
    answer: "With the & operator",
    options: [
      "With the & operator",
      "With the ref word",
      "With the * operator",
      "With the REF word"
    ]
  },
];